[
{
    "question":"Ursa Major Solar tracks both user issues and customer issues.<ul><li>A user issue can be logged as: new, waiting for reply, closed</li><li>A customer issue can be logged as: new, working, closed</li></ul>An administrator needs to track both case types. Which features should be used?",
    "options":
    ["Page Layouts and Record Types",
    "Page Layouts and Process Builder",
    { "option": "Record Types and Support Processes", "explanation": "Record types let you offer different business processes, picklist values, and page layouts to different users." },
    "Workflows and Automated Case Users"
    ],
    "answers":["C"]
}, {
    "question":"Salesforce users at Universal Containers complain that global search returns too many records.<br>Which two configurations should a System Administrator perform to help users manage search results? Choose 2 options.",
    "options":
    ["Enable Sidebar Search Auto-Complete in the object's search settings.",
    "Specify the Search Filter Fields for the object's search layout.",
    "Reduce the number of records displayed for each object in the Search Results page.",
    "Specify the Keywords and include them into the object's search layout."
    ],
    "answers":["B", "C"]
}, {
    "question":"Which two objects can be related to Campaign Members? Choose 2 options.",
    "options":
    [{ "option": "Leads", "explanation": "Campaign members are contacts or leads associated with campaigns." },
    "Contact Roles",
    "Partners",
    "Contacts"
    ],
    "answers":["A", "D"]
}, {
    "question":"Ursa Major Solar's administrator created a new account record type, but when marketing users are creating new account records, they are unable to choose the new record type.<br>What are two potential causes of this issue? Choose 2 options.",
    "options":
    [{ "option": "The record type is deactivated.", "explanation": "Record types need to be active in order for users to access them." },
    { "option": "The record type is disassociated from the page layout.", "explanation": "The record type is not populated by the page layout relationship." },
    { "option": "The record type default setting is disabled.", "explanation": "A record type can be active or inactive." },
    { "option": "The record type is disabled on the marketing user profile.", "explanation": "Record types need to be assigned to a profile." }
    ],
    "answers":["A", "D"]
}, {
    "question":"Universal Containers wants to allow potential customers to submit Cases for technical inquiries. They do not have resources to set up a call center and need to make support available through another means.<br>Which two options should they consider? Choose 2 options.",
    "options":
    [{ "option": "Implement a Lightning Partner Community with Knowledge.", "explanation": "Partner communities and knowledge articles can't submit cases to support." },
    { "option": "Generate Web-to-Case HTML code to add to the website.", "explanation": "Gather customer support requests directly from a website and automatically generate new cases with Web-to-Case. Setting up Web-to-Case involves enabling the feature, choosing settings, and adding the Web-to-Case form to your website." },
    { "option": "Adding a link for Auto-Response Rules for Solutions.", "explanation": "A link and auto-response rules can't submit cases to support." },
    { "option": "Adding a link to a specified routing address for Email-to-Case.", "explanation": "Set up Email-to-Case to efficiently resolve customer issues. Salesforce automatically creates cases and auto-populates case fields when customers send messages to the specified email addresses." }
    ],
    "answers":["B", "D"]
}, {
    "question":"Universal Containers has a team of Account Managers that requested email alerts any time an Opportunity or Case is created on Accounts that they own.<br>What is the minimum number of workflows needed to accomplish this task?",
    "options":
    [{ "option": "One workflow rule with two email alerts", "explanation": "" },
    { "option": "Four workflow rules for create and update on Opportunities and Accounts", "explanation": "" },
    { "option": "No workflow rules, but two email alerts", "explanation": "" },
    { "option": "Two workflow rules with one email alert each", "explanation": "Workflow rules are specific to each object." }
    ],
    "answers":["D"]
}, {
	"question":"The Password Policy shows that the length of time until passwords expire is 90 days. However, some users find that their passwords expire every 30 days.s2<br>Where should the System Administrator change the password expiration period for these users?",
	"options":
	["Roles assigned to the Users",
	{"option":"Profiles assigned to the Users",
	"explanation":"Changes to org-wide password policies don't apply to users of a profile that has its own password policies."},
	"Individual User records",
	"Permission Sets assigned to the Users"],
	"answers":["B"]
}, {
	"question":"A sales executive at Universal Containers wants to be notified whenever high-value opportunities are created for hot accounts. What should an administrator do to meet this requirement?",
	"options":
	["Create an escalation rule based on the opportunity amount.",
	"Create a validation rule that evaluates the account rating.",
	"Create an auto-response rule on the opportunity object.",
	{"option":"Create a workflow rule on the opportunity object.",
	"explanation":"Automate your organization's standard process by creating a workflow rule."}],
	"answers":["D"]
}, {
	"question":"Ursa Major Solar wants all Sales Users to see a dashboard that displays Total Closed/Won Opportunity Amount by User on a monthly basis. The Opportunity sharing model is private.<br>What should the administrator do to fulfill this request?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Request for the Sales Manager to create the Dashboard from the Opportunities by User Report and save it to her private Dashboards Folder.",
	"explanation":"Saving to a private folder will not allow access for the Sales users."},
	{"option":"Create the Dashboard from the Opportunities by User Report, choose the Sales Manager as RunAs User and Save in the private Dashboard Folder.",
	"explanation":"Saving to a private folder will not allow access for the Sales users."},
	{"option":"Create the Dashboard from the Opportunities by User Report, then save it in the shared Dashboard Folder as a Dynamic Dashboard.",
	"explanation":"Dynamic dashboard would only show data the running users has access too."},
	{"option":"Request for the Sales Manager to create the Dashboard from the Opportunities by User Report, select \"View Dashboard as Me\", and save in the shared Dashboard Folder.",
	"explanation":"By setting the running user to the Sales Manager and saving in a shared folder the Sales user will see all the records the Sales Manager can see."}],
	"answers":["D"]
}, {
	"question":"A Finance user with the \"View All Data\" permission enabled sees no Opportunities when opening a Sales pipeline report. However, a Sales Rep sees Opportunities as expected.<br>Which two actions should a System Administrator perform to resolve this problem?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Select Save Hierarchy Level on the pipeline report.","explanation":"Show the hierarchy to see your org's role hierarchy above the report results. You can use the role hierarchy to share report data with people at different levels in the hierarchy."},
	{"option":"Change the Org-Wide Opportunity Sharing Default to Public Read."},
	{"option":"Update the report filter to show All Opportunities.","explanation":"Use filters to pare down a report until it only shows the data that is needed."},
	{"option":"Create a Custom Report Type for the user that shows all records."}],
	"answers":["A","C"]
}, {
	"question":"An administrator at Ursa Major Solar is configuring password requirements for the company's users.<br>Which three actions are administrators able to configure? Choose 3 options.",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Set maximum invalid login attempts."},
	{"option":"Set password complexity requirements."},
	{"option":"Set prohibited password values."},
	{"option":"Set requirement that passwords must be unique for each user."},
	{"option":"Set the length of time before passwords expire.","explanation":"The length of time until a user password expires and must be changed defaults to 90 days. An admin is also able to change this setting to an expiration date that's earlier or later than the default expiration date, or set it to never expire."}],
	"answers":["A","B","E"]
}, {
	"question":"The administrator for the Cloud Kicks has a flow that makes several updates to Contacts when they are being created. If the Contact Status is \"New\" and the Contact's email is known, the administrator would also like to send a welcome email.<br>What should the administrator do to complete this requirement?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Create a process builder with email alert to send the email."},
	{"option":"Create a workflow rule with email alert to send the email."},
	{"option":"Update the flow with a formula to send the email when needed."},
	{"option":"Update the flow with a decision to send the email when needed.","explanation":"When a flow executes a Decision element, it evaluates each decision outcome in order."}],
	"answers":["D"]
}, {
	"question":"An administrator for Ursa Major Solar wants to allow internal users to view a dashboard as a Sales Manager within a given sales region.<br>How can this be configured?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Create a dashboard to run as the logged-in user."},
	{"option":"Create a dashboard for all opportunities in the region."},
	{"option":"Create a dashboard to run as a specified user.","explanation":"This dashboard would show the specified users information properly."},
	{"option":"Create a dashboard with multiple components."}],
	"answers":["C"]
}, {
	"question":"A System Administrator wants to implement a feature for call recording to monitor customer service quality using Salesforce Service Cloud.<br>Which two statements regarding call recording should be considered when implementing this requirement? Choose 2 options.",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Call recording is a feature of some add-on products from the AppExchange.","explanation":"Use the AppExchange to find solutions for complex processes."},
	{"option":"Call recording is a native feature available with Salesforce by default."},
	{"option":"Call recording is a feature that will not work with Salesforce Service Cloud."},
	{"option":"Call recording is a feature that a developer might create with Salesforce App Cloud.","explanation":"Use a developer to code to create solutions for complex processes."}],
	"answers":["A","D"]
}, {
	"question":"Custom fields in the Lead object can be mapped to which two types of fields? Choose 2 options.",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Custom Account","explanation":"Custom lead fields allow custom information to convert to custom fields in accounts, contacts, and opportunities."},
	{"option":"Standard Contact"},
	{"option":"Custom Activity"},
	{"option":"Custom Opportunity"}],
	"answers":["A","D"]
}, {
	"question":"What should a System Administrator configure to provide each Sales Rep a dashboard that shows their current Opportunity pipeline?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Set the Dashboard Running User to the current user.","explanation":"This ensures that the dashboard shows data relevant to only the user viewing it. The dashboard viewer allows the dashboard readers see data as themselves, according to their own access to data. These types of dashboards are often called dynamic dashboards."},
	{"option":"Set a Dashboard filter to the current user.","explanation":"Setting the dashboard filter to the current user would only show opportunities for that user, not the user running the dashboard."},
	{"option":"Create a dashboard folder for each user.","explanation":"Creating a dashboard folder for each user would not filter the dashboard for users. A dashboard folder is for storing dashboards, limiting visibility to the dashboards in the folder."},
	{"option":"Create a dashboard for each user."},
	{"option":"FILTER THE DASHBOARD WITH A DYNAMIC VIEW SET TO THE VP OF SALES.","explanation":"Dynamic dashboards are limited. The View Dashboard As options are: Me, Another person, Dashboard viewer"}],
	"answers":["A"]
}, {
	"question":"Users at Universal Containers (UC) adhere to the following process for expense reports:<ul><li>Create the expense report.</li><li>Attach receipts in an Expenses app.</li><li>Send the report to the accountant to review and approve.</li></ul>An administrator needs to enable this app for Salesforce Mobile.<br>What should the administrator consider from the User's perspective?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"A user can create list views, attach receipts as photos, and submit records for approval."},
	{"option":"A user can utilize Search, create list views, and receive record push notifications from Chatter."},
	{"option":"A user can create records, attach receipts as photos, and submit for approval."},
	{"option":"A user can search Salesforce Records, attach receipts as photos, and approve records from Chatter."}],
	"answers":["C"]
}, {
	"question":"Ursa Major Solar (USM) has a Web-to-Case form on its Lightning Customer Community. USM wants to separate Cases into the following product categories:<ul><li>Residential</li><li>Lots/Land</li><li>Commercial</li></ul>USM has added a picklist field to store this data.<br>How can the Case be automatically placed in the correct queue upon submission?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Create Record Types for each picklist value and a Business Process to move each Case to the correct Queue."},
	{"option":"Create an Escalation Rule entry for each picklist value and set to zero minutes."},
	{"option":"Create Assignment Rules based on the picklist values to move Cases to a Queue.","explanation":"Assignment Rules define conditions that determine how leads or cases are processed. The rules assign leads and cases to the specified user or queue."},
	{"option":"Create Record Types for each picklist value and assign to each product team's profile."}],
	"answers":["C"]
}, {
	"question":"The marketing team is asked to provide branding and messaging for email templates to be used throughout the customer support process.<br>In which two locations can the System Administrator implement customer-facing email templates with respect to Cases? Choose 2 options.",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Support Reps' Send Email options","explanation":"These options let you create email templates for support users."},
	{"option":"Case Auto-response Rules","explanation":"Auto-response rules let you automatically send email responses to lead or case submissions based on the record's attributes."},
	{"option":"Case Escalation Notifications"},
	{"option":"Owner Assignment Notifications"}],
	"answers":["A","B"]
}, {
	"question":"Which two changes are tracked in the Setup Audit Trail? Choose 2 options.",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Using the Data Import Wizard"},
	{"option":"Using the Data Loader"},
	{"option":"Creating a List View"},
	{"option":"Resetting a user's password"}],
	"answers":["A","D"]
}, {
	"question":"Ursa Major Solar recently acquired a company whose sales team has a unique sales process, with stages that are different from the current setup of stages in Salesforce.<br>The Chief Technology Officer (CTO) has decided that the new sales team should NOT change their process at all. What should the administrator do to incorporate the new sales team's process?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Create a record type and page layout for the new sales team and a custom field for the new stages."},
	{"option":"Create new values for the opportunity stage field; create a new sales process assigned to a custom record type for the new sales team.","explanation":"Record types let you offer different business processes, picklist values, and page layouts to different users."},
	{"option":"Create new values for the opportunity stage field; order them so that the new Sales team's values are at the bottom of the picklist."},
	{"option":"Create new values for the opportunity stage field and use field-level security to control which teams see which fields."}],
	"answers":["B"]
}, {
	"question":"At Ursa Major Solar, Salesforce users have a session timeout of 12 hours. Management wants the session timeout to be increased to 24 hours. Management also wants inactive users to be logged out at that time. What should the administrator do to fulfill this request?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"In session settings, select 24 hours, and check the box for force logout on session timeout."},
	{"option":"In session settings, select 24 hours, and uncheck the box for force logout on session timeout."},
	{"option":"In user profiles, type in 24 hours in the timeout section, and uncheck the box for force logout on session timeout."},
	{"option":"In user profiles, enter 24 hours in the timeout section, and check the box for force logout on session timeout."}],
	"answers":["A"]
}, {
	"question":"How can multiple Campaign records be associated with a single Opportunity?",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Campaign Hierarchy"},
	{"option":"Campaign Influence"},
	{"option":"Primary Campaign Source","explanation":"Primary campaign source is a picklist."},
	{"option":"Campaign Members","explanation":"Campaign members are contacts or leads associated with campaigns."}],
	"answers":["B"]
}, {
	"question":"Which two actions should an administrator perform to provide a sales team with an easy solution for gathering customer requirements and sharing presentations with their customers? Choose 2 options.",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Ensure opportunity teams are created for customers.","explanation":"Opportunity teams are for internal users."},
	{"option":"Add customers to libraries.","explanation":"External customers cannot be added to Libraries."},
	{"option":"Use Salesforce Files to post presentations in Chatter.","explanation":"Post files to a Chatter customer group."},
	{"option":"Add customers to private Chatter groups.","explanation":"Create a Chatter customer group. Customers can see only the groups they're invited to. They can interact only with members of those groups."}],
	"answers":["C","D"]
}, {
	"question":"Which two levels of access should be set when sharing a document folder with users? Choose 2 options.",
	"options":
	[{"option":"Read/Write"},
	{"option":"Read/Write/Create/Delete","explanation":"An admin would not want users to be able to delete content."},
	{"option":"Read/Write/Create"},
	{"option":"Read-only"}],
	"answers":["A","D"]
},


{
    "question":"",
    "options":
    [{ "option": "", "explanation": "" },
    { "option": "", "explanation": "" },    
    { "option": "", "explanation": "" },
    { "option": "", "explanation": "" }
    ],
    "answers":[""]
}

 
]